Career Information
Examinations
Career News
If you're unsure about your career,
it's time to take the first step.
Gala Concert
（公生）《音楽準備室に来れば
会えると思ったんだけど》
I thought if I came to the music room, you would be here.
But I don't have any means of contacting you.
《連絡の取りようがないよ》
《電話番号も
メアドも知らない》
I don't know your phone number or even your email address.
《僕は　君のこと
何も知らないんだな》
I...
don't know anything about you, do I?
（椿）公生！
うっ！
Kousei!
かをちゃんが
倒れて入院したって。
It's Kao...
She collapsed and was sent to the hospital.
TOTSUHARA UNIVERSITY HOSPITAL
（かをり）よっ。　どうだった？
Hey there! How'd it go yesterday?
昨日　連絡しようと思ったんだけどちょっと無理っぽくて→
I was going to contact you, but I couldn't in the end.
辞退してもらえたらいいかなって。
I wanted to ask for you to withdraw...
行けなくて　ごめんね。
I'm sorry I couldn't make it.
（椿）ねえ　何　買った？
（渡）ヨシトモのケーキ。→
Hey, what did you get her?
Some cake from Yoshitomo.
女の子は好きだろ。
彼女んち　ケーキ屋だよ。
Girls like that stuff, right?
Her family runs a cake shop, you know.
（渡）こういうのは　気持ちだよ。
It's the thought that's important here.
Here we are!
来たー！
いらっしゃい。
Welcome!
お土産　持ってきた。
ありがとう。
We brought gifts!
Thanks!
How do you feel?
どう？　体調。
ピンピンだよ。
Never better! I'm just staying over for tests.
単なる検査入院だもん。
Did you miss seeing me?
（渡）俺に会えなくて
さみしかった？
フフフ。　さみしかったよー。
I sure did!
《短期間に　２回も》
Twice in such a short time...
（公生）検査入院は
この前もしたよね？
But weren't you admitted to take tests just the other day?
That was for some new tests which weren't really that big of a deal.
この前　まあ　いっかって
やってない検査。
一応　頭だし。
Anyway, this is for my head.
今回は　静養も兼ねて
時間をかけてね。
This time, it's also so I can rest up, and take more time to heal.
今　いやらしい目で
視姦したでしょ？
Were you just looking at me with a dirty gleam in your eyes?!
所構わず　欲情して！　病人よ！
Giving in to your desires! Do you know where you are?!
I'm an invalid! Or is that why you're doing it?!
病人だからか！？
してない！　欲情してない！
I'm not! I'm not giving in to anything!
俺は欲情した！
Well, I sure did!
But that was a serious shocker.
（渡）でも　びっくりしたよ。→
You don't show up, and next we hear, you're in the hospital.
来ないと思ったら
入院してるんだもん。
It was a shock for me too!
私だって　びっくりしたよ。
ふらついて　頭ぶつけたら…。
《うわっ》
I stumbled, hitting my head after...
Then blood came gushing out! It was a mess all over, okay! A mess!
血が　ドバーっと出るんだもん。
ドバーっとよ　ドバーっと。
私　どん引き！
I was so stunned!
お父さんたちが
取り乱しちゃって　病院　直行。
My parents totally lost it and sent me right to the hospital.
で　現在に至る。
あっ　私　イチジクタルト。
And now, here I am.
Oh, I'll take the fig tart!
もともと疲れやすいんだけど→
I've always been the type to get tired easily, but lately I've been using up a lot of energy.
最近は　エネルギー使うことが
多かったから→
頑張り過ぎちゃった。
I guess I pushed myself too hard.
Wiggle
Yum!
Yet she's burning energy as she eats.
Wiggle
《食べながら
エネルギー使ってる》
Wiggle
（渡）本も持ってきた！
入院生活　暇でしょ？
Wiggle
I brought you some books too!
You've got nothing to do in here, right?
（椿）おおっ。　これ図書館の本？
無断で持ってきたの？
Witch's Apprentice
Fly Me to the Moon
Starlit Hill
MOVED BY MUSIC
Are these books from the library?
Did you take them without permission?
（渡）音楽関係のやつもあるよ。
There are some about music too.
こんなに　たくさんあっても
しょうがないじゃない。
What's she gonna do with a ton of books?
何でよ？
What's the problem?
Well, you'll be coming back to school by the second semester, right?
だって　かをちゃん　２学期には
学校に来れるんだよね？
うん　もちろんだよ。
Yes, of course I will.
（渡）へえ　そうなんだ　よかったね。《気のせいだ》
It must be my imagination.
《今の返答　あらかじめ
用意してたみたいだなんて》
That answer just now...
seemed like something that was rehearsed.
ハハハ…。
（渡）じゃあね　かをりちゃん。→
All right then, Kaori. I'll be seeing you in my dreams.
夢の中で会おうね…。
（椿）うるさい。　バイバーイ。
Shut up. Bye!
Bye!
バイバーイ。
My Sweet Accomplice     Mita Masahiro
Welcome,
Debussy!
こんなに読む時間　ないよ。
I don't have time to read all these...
My Sweet Accomplice     Mita Masahiro
（看護師）かをりちゃん。
はい。
Kaori?
MEDICATION ROOM
Yes?
お友達　帰った？
はい。
Have your friends gone home?
Yes.
（看護師）じゃあ　いい？
はい。
Then can we begin?
Yes.
Please resume the IV drip.
点滴の続き　お願いします。
Saitou
Oh!
（柏木）「おっ」て何よ。
（椿）先輩からメール。→
What was that?
My boyfriend just texted me.
"Let's go to the festival today," he says.
今日　お祭り　行こうって。
Boyfriend? You mean Saitou?
（柏木）先輩って　斉藤先輩？
まだ　別れてなかったの？
You haven't broken up yet?
Of course not!
（椿）当ったり前じゃん！
（柏木）何で？
Why?
何でって…。
What do you mean?
嫌いになったわけじゃないし。
It's not like I don't like him anymore.
Then do you like him?
（柏木）じゃあ　好き？
（椿）そりゃ　憧れてた先輩だし。
Well, of course.
I've always had a crush on him.
（柏木）じゃあ　有馬君は？
Then...
What about Arima?
《椿》
Tsubaki?
Tsubaki!
《椿》
（椿）なっ…。
Why...
Why are you bringing up Kousei, of all people?
何で　今
公生の名前が出てくんのよ。
ハハッ！
バ　バ…　バカじゃないの？
Th-That's so ridiculous!
公生は…。
Kousei is...
（椿）ちっちゃいころから
何するにも一緒で→
Ever since we were little,
we've always done everything together,
and rather than seeing him as a guy,
異性っていうより
弟って感じだよ。
I see him as a kid brother.
Kid brother again?
（柏木）また　弟？→
あんたは　弟　弟って呪文を唱えて
暗示をかけてるの。→
Are you trying to jinx yourself by chanting over and over that he's your kid brother?
そうしないと怖いんだ。→
I bet you're too scared not to.
今の居心地のいい関係が
壊れてしまうから。
Because if you don't, the comfortable relationship
you have right now would be destroyed.
（椿）ふんっ！
（柏木）ほあっ！
Hey!
渾身のだし巻き卵がー！
I was saving that omelette for last!
そんなんじゃないって
言ってんじゃん。
I told you, it's not like that!
I chose the wrong way to approach this.
（柏木）《攻め方　間違えた》
What's up with you?!
何よ。
Arima was afraid, but he still took the plunge.
（柏木）《有馬君は
怖くても踏みだしたわよ》
（柏木）いつか　取り返しが
つかなくなるんだからな。
Someday, there'll be no turning back, you know?
Suwa
Shrine
（斉藤）おお　浴衣。
（椿）あっ…。
Hey, a yukata!
（斉藤）よく似合ってる。
It looks good on you!
You look really cute in it.
すごいカワイイよ。
アハハ。　いいですよ
気を使わなくたって。
Suwa
Shrine
Hey, you don't have to be nice.
馬子にも衣装ってね。
Anybody can look good in the right clothes!
（椿）《ほら　みろ　柏木》→
What did I tell you, Kashiwagi?
《公生は
こんなこと言ってくれない》→
Kousei would never say that to me.
Because he only sees me...
《私のことなんて→
as a nagging big sister or something.
口うるさい姉ちゃんぐらいにしか
思ってないんだから》→
《きっと。　どうせ…》
I'm sure of it.
Anyway...
Today's the day of the festival, huh?
今日　お祭りなんだね。
うん。
Yeah.
立ってないで座ったら？
Don't just stand there. Have a seat.
Well, okay.
あっ　いや　やっぱり立ってる。
On second thought, I'll keep standing.
You sure are fidgety.
落ち着かないのね。　挙動不審。
You're acting suspicious.
病院が　苦手なんだ。
I don't like hospitals.
《大丈夫だよね？》
You're going to be okay, right?
《検査は　嘘じゃないよね？》
You're not lying about being tested, right?
《もう　学校に来ないなんて
言わないよね？》
You're not going to tell me you're
never coming back to school, right?
《また　いつもみたいに
悪態つくよね？》
You'll be back to chewing me out again, right?
《音楽準備室で話せるよね？》
We can talk in the music room again, right?
君は…。
さっきまで　渡君が来てたの。
You—
Watari was just here, actually.
これ　お土産。
He brought me this.
Watari.
《渡》
知らなかった。
I had no idea that you played alone at the gala concert.
君　ガラコン
一人で弾いたんだって？
Watari told me all about it.
渡君から聞いたよ。
あっ　うん。
Yeah...
The accompanist playing a solo? That's a first!
伴奏者がソロでなんて
あり得ないよね。
どんだけ出たがりなんだよ。
What kind of a show-off are you?
It was a concert for violinists,
so that just makes it more ridiculous!
バイオリンのガラコンなのに
意味　分かんない。
笑かさないでよ。　バカなの？
おなか痛ーい。
Don't make me laugh! Are you an idiot? My sides!
《誰のせいだよ！》
Whose fault was it?!
どうして？　辞退しても
みんな当然だって思うよ。
Why did you play?
Anyone would've expected you to withdraw.
初めは　君がバカにされたから。
At first...
it was because someone insulted you.
Then midway through, the sound disappeared.
でもね　途中から　音が消えて→
母さんの言葉や　しぐさや　におい。
My mom's words, her gestures, her smell.
母さんとの思い出が
音になって空に舞い上がってた。
My memories of her turned into notes, and flew away into the sky.
そう。
I see.
君は　どうしたって
表現者なんだね。
You're an artist no matter what, aren't you, Arima Kousei?
有馬　公生君。
Just as I thought.
《ああ　やっぱり》
She chose that piece for me.
《あの選曲は
僕のための選曲だったんだ》
《『愛の悲しみ』　この曲は
母さんを思い出させる》
"Love's Sorrow."
This piece evokes memories of my mother.
The scent of fabric softener.
《柔軟剤のにおい》
《寝ぼけ眼に聞こえるピアノ》
The sound of the piano as I looked up drowsily.
《控えめな子守歌》
The quiet lullaby.
《消毒液のにおい》
The smell of antiseptic.
《響く足音》
The echoes coming from the footsteps.
《白く濁った　リノリウムの床》
The cloudy and white linoleum floor.
《君と　重なる》
They're all overlapping with you.
Welcome.
（早希）《いらっしゃい》
I wish I could've heard you play.
聴きたかったな　君のピアノ。
《平気だよね？》
You're okay, right?
また一緒に　弾きたかったな。
I wish I could've played with you again.
You're going to be fine, right?
《大丈夫だよね？》
《検査は嘘じゃないよね？》
You're not lying about the tests, right?
You're not going to tell me you're
never coming back to school, right?
《もう学校に来ないなんて
言わないよね？》
I can see you again, right?
《また　会えるよね》
２回目だ。
えっ？
That's the second time.
What?
君が　僕の名前を呼んだの。
That you called me by my name.
《君は…》
You...
You won't leave me...
《君は　母さんみたいに
いなくならないよね》
like my mother did, will you?
Your Lie in April
The Sumiya Baseball Youth Sports Club special boot camp for sluggers will now begin!
（椿）《これより
墨谷野球スポーツ少年団→
強打者養成特訓を開始する！》
《え～！》
《海　入りたい！》
Huh?
I wanna go swimming!
I wanna play games!
《ゲームしたい！》
（椿）《うるさーい！》
Shut up! Ten sets of ten sprints down the beach! Now, get to it!
《砂浜ダッシュ　１０本
１０セット！　始め！》
（椿）《ふん！》
（子供たち）《ううっ…》
I don't even play baseball, so how come I have to do this?
（公生）
《僕　野球してないよ。　何で？》
Even people who play the piano
need to build up their legs! I think!
（椿）《ピアノ弾く人も
足腰　大事！　たぶん！》
Huh? You said "I think!"
《ええ！？　たぶんって言った！》
（椿）《あっ　ちっちゃい足跡》
Tiny footprints...
They are not! It's just that your feet are huge.
《違うよ！
椿の足が　でかいだけだ》
What?! That's not how you talk to a girl!
《何だと！　乙女に向かって！》
《わあー！》
Come back here, you!
（椿）《待てー！　こらー！》
（子供たち）《わあー！》
（椿）《公生　王二公園　行こうよ》
Kousei, let's go to Ouji Park!
I wish I could, but I've got piano lessons.
（公生）《行きたいけど　僕
ピアノのレッスンがあるから》
（椿）《ちぇっ　せっかく
虹色に輝く泥団子→
Hmph.
I was gonna show him a mud ball as shiny as a rainbow!
見せてやろうと思ったのに》
《われながら　いい出来だわ。
傑作だわ》
Great job, if I do say so myself!
A masterpiece!
I know! I'll make one for Kousei too.
（椿）《そうだ
公生にも作ってやろ》
Kousei, let's play catch. I just learned how to throw a sinker.
《公生　キャッチボールやろう。
シンカー　覚えたんだ》
Kousei's going to be a pianist, so he's busy.
《公生君は　ピアニストになるんだから
忙しいのよ》
《おてて　ケガしたら
どうするの》
What would he do if he hurt his hands?
Scrub, scrub.
（椿）《ごしごし》
《ごめん》
Sorry.
（椿）《ごしごし　ごしごし
ごしごし》
Scrub, scrub.
Scrub, scrub, scrub, scrub.
（女の子）
《有馬君　大会近いから→
I hear Arima's skipping school to practice the
piano since he's got a competition coming up.
学校お休みして
ピアノの練習なんだって》
（男の子）《ずりぃ～》
No fair!
Music
《さんはい》
（子供たち）《♪♪「おお　ブレネリ」》
Three, two...
Music for Children
O Vreneli, where is your home?
（子供たち）
《♪♪「あなたの　お家はどこ」》→
Music for Children
My home is in Switzerland.
《♪♪「私の　お家は
スイッツランドよ」》→
Music for Children
It is by the beautiful lake.
《♪♪「きれいな湖水の
ほとりなのよ」》→
Music for Children
Yo ho ho, tra la la la.
《♪♪「ヤッホ　ホトゥラララ」》
（椿）《音楽なんて大嫌い》
I hate music!
ちゃんと練習してんの？
Are you really practicing?
見てないからって
サボってんでしょ！
You're slacking off because I'm not around, aren't you?!
You don't have to tell me to practice!
言われなくても　やってるよ！
I do every single day. Both Hanon and Czerny, okay?!
毎日　毎日
ハノンも　チェルニーも！
That's nowhere close to enough! Get some Chopin in there!
全然　少ない！　ショパンもやれ！
いつ寝ればいいんだよ。
リストもやれ！
So tell me when I'm supposed to sleep!
Practice Liszt too!
I don't know what this is about, but calm down.
よく分かんないけど落ち着いて！
いっそ　もう寝るんじゃねえ！
分かんない話　しないでよね。
Don't talk about stuff we don't understand.
嫌だー！
手　動かせー！
I wonder...
（柏木）何だかな。
Leave her alone.
ほっとけよ。
I'm turning to you because I can't do that!
ほっとけないから
相談してんでしょ。
俺は
俺に　ほれない女に興味はない。
I'm not interested in girls who aren't in love with me.
（柏木）いっそ　すがすがしいわ。
All the more refreshing!
人から　違うでしょって言われるとふてくされて意固地になって→
If someone tells her, "You're wrong,"
you know she's gonna sulk and get all stubborn, and then things will get complicated.
ややこしくなるに
決まってるんだから。
公生のことに関しては　特にね。
Especially when it comes to Kousei.
Apple
As much as I don't want to, I have to agree.
（柏木）《同感。　嫌だけど》→
《でも　私は
椿には笑っててほしい》
But I want Tsubaki to smile again.
（渡）ぼろぼろになろうと
何だろうと→
Even if she gets all bruised and battered,
Tsubaki's still gonna have to realize it herself.
椿が自分で気付くしかねえよ。→
She's going to have to realize the fact that the guy by her side isn't her kid brother at all.
そばにいる男は
弟なんかじゃないってことを。
（部員）
渡先輩　ミニゲーム始めますよー。
Watari, the scrimmage is about to start!
おう！
Right!
ジュース　サンキュー。
Thanks for the juice!
サンキュー。
Thanks.
（柏木）《でも　それってさ…》
But that kind of thing...
たいてい　手遅れになってから
気付くもんだよね。
Usually, you don't realize it till it's too late.
（教師）おい　有馬。
あっ　はい。
Hey, Arima.
Yes?
Have you made up your mind yet?
そろそろ決めたか？
You're the only holdout in my class.
うちのクラスで　お前だけだぞ。
まだなの。
うん？
志望校だよ。　進路。
I'm talking about what career path you want to follow.
My career...
進路。
《思ったんです。
変なピアニストになりたいなって》
That's what made me think...
I'd like to become a really weird pianist!
You should give it some thought, but don't take too long.
（教師）考えるのもいいが
早めにな。
はい。
All right.
《進路　将来…》
My career.
My future...
《僕は
何者になりたいんだろう？》
Who do I want to become?
He dropped it on the beach and wouldn't stop crying, so I gave him my popsicle.
（椿）砂浜に落としちゃって
泣きやまないから→
私のアイスバーあげたんです。
（斉藤）ハハッ。
そしたら
ミルク味がよかったって。
And then he says he wished it was milk-flavored!
あっ　あの…。
すみません。　また私。
Sorry, there I go again...
いいよ。　楽しいよ。　有馬君の話。
《やっちった！》
It's okay. It's fun to hear about Arima.
I did it again!
家が　お隣さんだから
思い出が一緒だもんな。
You live next door to each other, so of course you have the same memories.
He's like your kid brother, right?
弟みたいなもんだな。
No, he's not! I'm not Kousei's babysitter!
違います！　私は
公生のお守りじゃありません！
Then what am I?
（椿）《じゃあ　何？》→
《家が隣同士》→
We're next-door neighbors.
《私より　ちっちゃくて
早くに　お母さんを亡くして→
He's the boy who's smaller than me, who lost his
mother at a young age, who I can't help but look after.
ほっとけない
元気になってほしかった男の子》
And the one I wished would get back on his feet.
[TEL]（柏木）バカじゃないの。
What are you, an idiot?
Use your heart to solve those kinds of problems.
[TEL]（柏木）そういう問題は
心を使うもんよ。
Oh, come on!
もう　何よ！　こないだから
訳分かんないことばっか。
I can't make sense of what you're saying these days!
[TEL]あんたは　この前→
The other day, you told me that you "didn't dislike" Saitou, but...
斉藤先輩のこと　嫌いじゃないって言ってたけどさ。→
好きと　嫌いじゃないの間には
何億光年もの距離があるのよ。
"Like" and "don't dislike" are millions of light-years apart, you know?
好き？　嫌いじゃない？
意味　分かんない。
Like? Don't dislike? I don't know what you mean.
[TEL]あんたが素直になって
自覚しないと→
You need to be honest with yourself and admit it, or someone's going to get hurt.
そのうち傷つく人が出るよ。
Do you dislike me?
《俺のこと　嫌いか？》
That's crazy.
（椿）そんなこと。
憧れてた先輩だし。
You're the upperclassmen I always had a crush on.
（柏木）《じゃあ　好き？》
Then do you like him?
Who is it that I like?
（椿）《私は　誰が好き？》
（椿）好き。　嫌いじゃない。
好き。　嫌いじゃない。→
Like.
Don't dislike.
好き。　嫌いじゃない。
好き。　嫌いじゃない。→
Like.
Don't dislike.
好き。
Like.
公生。
Kousei?
ううー！
大丈夫か！？　ケガか？　病気か？
Are you okay?! Are you hurt? Sick? Did you get food poisoning?
食あたりか？　拾い食いするから！
You shouldn't scavenge for food!
I got a call from Kashiwagi saying you were in trouble!
柏木さんから　電話があって
椿が大変だって！
Huh?!
はあ～　だまされた。
Man, she sure got me.
柏木さんが　いたずらするなんて
あの人も　人の子だったんだ。
Who knew Kashiwagi would pull a prank like that?
So she's got another side to her, after all.
アハハハッ　柏木が言うと
変な迫力があるよね。
It has this strange impact, because it's coming from her.
It's not a laughing matter.
笑い事じゃないよ。
信じて走り回ったんだから。
I was running around like crazy because I believed her.
はぁー　すごい汗かいちゃった。
I'm dripping with sweat.
I want a popsicle!
アイスバー　食べたい。
Thank you very much!
（店員）ありがとうございました。
また　ミルク味？
Milk-flavored again?
これが好きなの。
It's what I like.
月が奇麗だ。
The moon's so pretty.
Well, I'm hearing it ad nauseam from the house next door!
隣の家から　嫌ってほど
聞こえてくるからね。
そんなに弾いてないよ。
I don't play it that much.
Talking like we always do.
（椿）《いつもの会話》
（椿）下手なの聞こえてきたよ。
I could hear some really lousy playing.
（椿）《じゃれ合うような冗談》
The banter and joking around.
（椿）《私より大きい。
男の子の足跡だ》
They're bigger than mine.
These are a boy's footsteps.
公生　何か　変わった。
Kousei, you've changed somehow.
えっ？　そう？
Really?
（椿）《変だな。　不意に目が合うと
心臓が　びっくりする》→
It's weird.
When our eyes happen to meet, my heart skips.
《きっと　夏が終わるせいだ》
変わったよ。　公生のことなんか→
I'm sure it's because summer is coming to an end.
Y-You did change. With you, I can tell right away.
すぐ分かる。
Your eyes sparkle now.
目が輝くようになった。
ピカーって　車のライトみたいに。
They light up, like headlights.
Especially...
（椿）特に
ピアノを弾いているとき→
when you're playing the piano.
優しさや　届けたいって思いが
あふれ出てた。→
This gentleness and yearning to convey something was pouring out of you.
It's like you're shouting to the world, "I'm right here!"
自分は　ここにいるんだって
叫んでるみたい。→
そういったものを届けられる
ピアニストなんだね。　公生は。
You're the kind of pianist who can convey all that, huh?
Maarui sekai no naka
On this beautiful Earth
You're an artist no matter what, aren't you?
《君は　どうしたって
表現者なんだね》
Kokyuu de kawasu kotoba
We can exchange words with a deep breath
椿。
（椿）うん？
Tsubaki?
Hm?
僕　音楽科のある高校に進むよ。
I'm going to go to a high school with a music course.
（椿）音楽科？
この辺にあったっけ？
Katachi nante nakutatte
Even though there’s no visible form,
Music course? Are there any around here?
No, so...
だから　家を出るよ。
I'll be leaving home.
Kokoro wa tsutau
Heart could convey our feelings
紘子さんも
週２ぐらい通えばいいって→
Hiroko said I only had to go to class twice a week or so.
言ってたし。
（椿）あれ…？
Huh?
Of course, I'm not sure that I'll get in.
もちろん　受かるか微妙だけど。
Shizuka ni kanjite
Quietly, I can feel it
Huh?
（椿）あれ…？
ブランクあるから。
I did sit out for a while.
Huh?
（椿）あれ？
あっ…。
Huh?
あれ？　あれ？
Kurenazumu ashioto
Sound of footsteps
（椿の泣き叫ぶ声）
（椿）《また。　まただ》→
It's happening again.
Ashita wo sagashiteru
Grow in the dark slowly
《音楽が公生を
遠くに連れていく》
Music is taking Kousei far away from me.
Ippo ippo kimi to hohaba awasete
Search for tomorrow, I match our paces step by step
You idiot, Kousei! You idiot!
（椿）《バカ。　バカ公生》→
《どこにでも行っちゃえ。
バカ公生》→
Go wherever you want, idiot!
《家が隣同士》→
We live next door to each other.
Kikoenai merodi
Inaudible melodies
《私より　ちっちゃくて→
He's the boy who's smaller than me,
早くにお母さんを亡くして→
who lost his mother at a young age,
Modokashiku hanete mo
How irritated, even bound you
who I can't help but look after.
ほっとけない
元気になってほしい男の子》→
Dare ni datte kesenai egao de tsumugou
But I will spin a smile that nobody could erase
And the one I wish would get back on his feet.
《このまま　ずっと→
To go on like this, for all time...
当たり前に
そばにいると思ってた男の子》→
The boy I took for granted
would always be by my side.
《ずっと　そばにいてほしい
男の子》
The boy I want to be by my side forever.
For you...
Tsubaki.
《椿》
あっ…。
Ano koro no merodi
The melodies of that time
Mou kikoenakute mo
Even if I cannot hear it anymore
Dare ni datte kesenai egao de tsumugou
But I will spin a smile that nobody could erase
For you...
I'm such an idiot...
（椿）私　バカだな。
《ごしごし　ごしごし》
Scrub, scrub, scrub, scrub.
《ウフフ　びっくりするかな　公生。ウフフ》
I wonder if Kousei will be surprised.
Episode 14
Footsteps
Episode 15
Liar
No two dreams can be the same
sore zore no yume wo erande
Episode 15
Liar
No two dreams can be the same
sore zore no yume wo erande
Watch next week too!